Contact

shadab14meb346@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-shadabalam (LinkedIn) www.shadab.info/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Node.js

React.js

JavaScript

Languages

Arabic (Elementary)

English

urdu

Certifications

Ethereum and Solidity: The Complete Developer's Guide

The Web Developer Bootcamp

Blockchain Architecture Design and Use Cases

JavaScript: Understanding the Weird Parts

MD SHADAB ALAM

Engineering Fellow at Pesto Tech

Hyderabad

Summary

Dedicated, enthusiastic and committed engineer with an on time and get it done attitude. Experience with full-stack web development using MERN stack. Technical proficiencies include.

Programming Languages: JavaScript, NodeJS

Frameworks: Express, ReactJS

Tools: Git, Postman

Methodologies:OOPs,Functional Programming

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services Assistant System Engineer November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

www.ixxo.io Blockchain-Intern September 2018 - October 2018 (2 months) Noida Area, India

Worked with go-ethereum implementation for the private network with POA consensus.

Education

Pesto Tech(Engineering Fellow)

Web Development Bootcamp · (2020 - 2020)

Aligarh Muslim University

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Mechanical Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

senior secondary school AMU

12th, Physics, mathematics, chemistry (2012 - 2014)